<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2016 Actinarium
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rhythm</string>
    <string name="app_title">Rhythm sample app</string>

    <string name="sample_header">Hello there!</string>
    <string name="copy_1">This here is small sample app to show off Rhythm library and inspire you to use it.
       Don’t forget to check out its <a href="https://github.com/Actinarium/Rhythm/tree/master/sample">source code</a> for complete experience.</string>

    <string name="copy_warning"><b>Hey!</b> Since you’re already judging, please report if you notice something <i>out of rhythm</i> (i.e. not aligned to 8dp/4dp grid), will you?</string>

    <string name="card_header">Intermission</string>
    <string name="card_text">Take a moment to appreciate this beautifully laid out card.</string>
    <string name="toggle">Toggle overlay</string>

    <string name="copy_2">Pull down the Notification shade to find Rhythm Quick Control. Loop through overlays for Activity background group.
        Then onto another groups. Knock yourself out!</string>

    <string name="copy_3">Yay! 0.9.2 introduces <b>declarative config</b>, making building overlays a breeze.
        Examine the <font face="monospace">/res/raw/overlay_config</font> to see how, or… Scratch that, try it out right here!</string>


    <string name="layer_types">Layer types</string>
    <string-array name="bullet_points">
        <item>Horizontal and vertical grid lines, repeating at a fixed step. Combine two grid line layers to make a square grid.</item>
        <item>Guides at arbitrary distance from specified view edge.</item>
        <item>Inset groups to clip and offset nested layers.</item>
        <item>Fill layers that can paint rectangular areas with uniform color to highlight margins.</item>
        <item>Dimensions labels, to inspect views’ dimensions at glance.</item>
        <item>More spec layer types coming soon!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="got_it">Got it</string>

    <string name="copy_4">While controlling overlays from the notification is convenient, sometimes you simply don’t need it.
        With Rhythm you can explicitly create unlinked groups, new drawables and overlays, and assign them programmatically (see the source).</string>

    <string name="copy_5">Thank you for following me to the end. If my calculations are correct, you should be <i>in love</i> with this library already, so why not support the developer?
        If you’re feeling generous, you can gift me a game on Steam, but simply telling your fellow developers about Rhythm or adding me to your circles is also awesome!
        Check out <a href="https://github.com/Actinarium/Rhythm">GitHub</a> to find out how you can help. &#9829;</string>
</resources>
