<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2016 Actinarium
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rhythm</string>
    <string name="app_title">Rhythm showcase</string>

    <string name="sample_header">Welcome to the Rhythm&#160;library sample app!</string>
    <string name="copy_1">This app demonstrates the capabilities of the&#160;library and how it can be&#160;used in a real&#160;project.
       You are welcome to examine its source&#160;code on&#160;<a href="https://github.com/Actinarium/Rhythm/tree/master/sample">GitHub</a>.</string>

    <string name="copy_warning"><b>Heads up!</b> If you see this, and the text in this sample is not aligned nicely to the 4dp baseline grid, please file an issue on GitHub with the screenshot and your device model. Thank you.</string>

    <string name="card_header">Details matter</string>
    <string name="card_text">— says designer marshmallow. Do you agree with her?</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="agree_msg">That’s the spirit!</string>
    <string name="disagree">Disagree</string>
    <string name="disagree_msg">Uhm… think again?</string>

    <string name="copy_2">Open the Notification drawer to access Rhythm Quick Control, which allows&#160;you to cycle through configurations without leaving your current&#160;screen.
        Go ahead and play&#160;around with overlays for different provided&#160;groups.</string>

    <string name="copy_3">As of v0.9, there are three <i>spec layer</i> types available out of the box for you to combine and make various overlays.
        Click the button to learn more.</string>
    <string name="layer_types">Layer types</string>
    <string-array name="bullet_points">
        <item>Horizontal and vertical grid lines, repeating at a fixed step, with optional offset and margins.
            Add two grid line layers to make a grid.\n</item>
        <item>Guides of arbitrary color and thickness, to make keylines and highlights.\n</item>
        <item>Dimensions label, to inspect view’s dimensions at glance.\n</item>
        <item>More spec layer types coming soon; meanwhile feel free to create your custom ones and show them to me!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="got_it">Got it</string>

    <string name="copy_4">While controlling overlays from the notification is convenient, sometimes you simply don’t need it.
        With Rhythm you can explicitly create unlinked groups, new drawables and overlays, and assign them programmatically (see the source).</string>

    <string name="copy_5">It’s not much yet, but if you already love this library and pictured how it would help you <i>tremendously</i> with
        your next project, motor over to <a href="https://github.com/Actinarium/Rhythm">GitHub</a> to learn how you can support the developer. &#9829;</string>
</resources>
